{	"div":
	[	
		{
			"Problem":"100/50",
			"answer":"100/50",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"684/57",
			"answer":"684/57",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"156/78",
			"answer":"156/78",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"186/93",
			"answer":"186/93",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"310/31",
			"answer":"310/31",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"1359/9",
			"answer":"1359/9",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"8836/5",
			"answer":"8836/5",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"2066/2",
			"answer":"2066/2",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"7234/6",
			"answer":"7234/6",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"7020/5",
			"answer":"7020/5",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"5098/6",
			"answer":"5098/6",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"7794/4",
			"answer":"7794/4",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"6125/9",
			"answer":"6125/9",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"9076/4",
			"answer":"9076/4",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"7661/5",
			"answer":"7661/5",
			"status":"unsolved"
		}

	]
}